http://unitedtty.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Your privacy is important to us. It is Unitedtty’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect from you across our website, unitedtty.com, and other sites we own and operate.
We only ask for personal information when we truly need it to provide a service to you. We collect it by fair and lawful means, with your knowledge and consent. We also let you know why we’re collecting it and how it will be used.
We only retain collected information for as long as necessary to provide you with your requested service. What data we store, we’ll protect within commercially acceptable means to prevent loss and theft, as well as unauthorised access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.
We don’t share any personally identifying information publicly or with third-parties, except when required to by law.
Our website may link to external sites that are not operated by us. Please be aware that we have no control over the content and practices of these sites, and cannot accept responsibility or liability for their respective privacy policies.
You are free to refuse our request for your personal information, with the understanding that we may be unable to provide you with some of your desired services.
Your continued use of our website will be regarded as acceptance of our practices around privacy and personal information. If you have any questions about how we handle user data and personal information, feel free to contact us.
Recent Posts
Removing the Old Window Type of Tint from Your Car
Bougainvillea Plants and the Right Way to Take Care of Them
House Carpet and Your Best Ways to Remove the Dirt Faster
Dreaming the Steps of a General Type of Working Contractor
Flooring Selection and the Best Strategies for You
Search for:
Recent Comments
United TTYRemoving the Old Window Type of Tint from Your Car August 3, 2020We tend to change the window tint of the car whenever we are thinking that it is going to be a bit dark to see the things from the outside or you are worried about the different kinds of problems that it has like the scratches and many more to mention here. Others would think […] secure_adminBougainvillea Plants and the Right Way to Take Care of Them July 31, 2020If you want to make your place more beautiful then you need to consider about growing some plants in your yard and this could be very achievable if you would think that you can do the best like planting more flowers that could attract the insects or you may want to plant more vegetables that […] secure_adminHouse Carpet and Your Best Ways to Remove the Dirt Faster July 29, 2020We all know that there are some people who are very picky when it comes to the design of the house and even when it comes to the decorations and the overall style of the rooms and to the flooring part of the home. We hire carpet cleaning In Yonkers just to ensure that you […] secure_adminDreaming the Steps of a General Type of Working Contractor July 27, 2020If you have the feelings and the ideas about constructions, then you need to consider about working as a contractor for general purposes and this will give you a nice and stable income in the future. Many men would think that this kind of job like the general contractor Newport Beach CA is easy since […] secure_adminFlooring Selection and the Best Strategies for You July 23, 2020It is not a joke for others to choose the best and the right flooring material for their homes and part of this one is to think deeply about the different kinds of materials that you can pick and it is not only about the design or the style but this one should be about […] secure_admin Archives
August 2020
July 2020
Categories
Car Services
Carpet Cleaning
Carpet cleaning In Yonkers
Construction Services
Wichita Falls Services
